Guide to the Doris Ulmann Photograph Collection ca. 1910-1934 PR 72
New-York Historical Society
- older, balding, light grey hair, oval eyeglasses, mustache, suit, vest, tie, seated [Phillips, John S., Editor, The American Magazine], 156208 (Item 3010)
  this is a photogravure print, DU copyright in lower left corner
- young, medium dark thick short hair, parted on side, round eyeglasses, suit, vest, patterned tie, seated holding a piece of paper [Haggard, Sewell, Editor, Everybody's], 156207 (Item 3011)
- seated in DU's studio chair, thin medium dark hair, high collar, mustache, holding eyeglasses [Adams, Henry Sherman, Editor, The Spur], 156206 (Item 3012)
  #2762-2768, 3012 same subject
- balding, patterned bow tie, suit, vest, seated at desk reading a book, right elbow resting on desk holding up his head [Whigham, Henry James, editor, Town and Country], 156205 (Item 3013)
  #816, 1203, 1228, 3013 same subject
- young, very dark straight short smooth hair, pencil thin mustache, pinstripe suit, vest, polka dot tie, seated, hands on knees [Hadden, Briton, Editor, Time], 156204 (Item 3014)
  this is a photo gravure print, DU copyright in lower left corner
- balding, medium dark hair, stout, seated, suit, vest, tie, monocle [Shipman, Louis Evan, Editor, Life], 156203 (Item 3015)
  #2097, 2163, 3015 same subject
- middle aged, balding, straight white hair, sideburns, mustache, beard, pince nez eyeglasses, jacket, vest, tie [Abbott, Lawrence F., Editor, The Outlook], 156202 (Item 3016)
  #2753-2757, 2979 same subject